Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Archives Moving Images Collection, ca. 1928-2001 UA.Film.Video
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Sports, I.
  - Football, 3.
    - Video, 648 items
      - Pitt / Miami #2, September 18, 1997; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 2 of ? (Box 26, Video 515)
      - Pitt vs SMU Tape 3 - 1982 Cotton Bowl, Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 3 of ? (Box 26, Video 517)
      - Pitt vs SMU Tape 4 - 1982 Cotton Bowl, Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 4 of ? (Box 26, Video 518)
      - Pitt - SMU (Cotton Bowl 1982) - 3, [DVD Available], 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 3 of ? Needs Case (Box 27, Video 525)
      - 1979 Pitt vs. Penn State #1, December 2, 1979; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 1 of ? (Box 27, Video 529)
      - 1979 Pitt vs. Penn State #2, December 2, 1979; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 2 of ? (Box 27, Video 520)
      - 1979 Pitt vs. Penn State #3, December 2, 1979; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 3 of ? (Box 27, Video 530)
      - 1991 Pitt Football, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBU-5 (Box 27, Video 522)
      - "Pat Cavanaugh" (Profile), unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 27, Video 526)
      - John Sutherland For Movietone, unknown; 1 Inch Videotape 480 Master Broadcast (Box 28, Video 534)
      - 1989 Pitt Panther Football - Radio Network Highlights, unknown; 1/4 Reel to Reel Audio (Box 28, Video 532)
      - Pitt Football Highlights, unknown; 1/4 Inch Videotape (Box 28, Video 538)
      - Bill Fralic, unknown; 2 Inch Quad Videotape (Box 28, Video 539)
      - Bill Fralic vs. Oklahoma, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBU 5 (Box 34, Video 697)
      - Bill Fralic vs. Oklahoma, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBU 5 Needs Case (Box 34, Video 701)
      - Bill Fralic (Profile), unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBU-5 (Box 43, Video 943)
      - 1978 Pitt / Penn State #4, November 24, 1978; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 29, Video 547)
      - The Johnny Majors Show - Show #4, September 24, 1994; VHS T-15 28:20 (Box 29, Video 571)
      - Pitt 3 Rutgers 1 - 11-11-95, November 11, 1995; VHS T-120 (Box 29, Video 576)
      - "Pitt at Villanova" (January 28, 1989) - "Paul Evans Show", VHS (Box 29, Video 577)
      - "1992-93 Pitt Basketball Senior Night" (Civic Arena), 1993; VHS T-120 (Box 29, Video 578)
      - Louis Riddick - University of Pittsburgh, Pitt Football Promo :30 Seconds, VHS T-30 (Box 29, Video 580)
      - Gregg Madsen QB, unknown; VHS T-120 Needs Case (Box 29, Video 582)
      - The 1993 Doak Walker Award "The National Running Back Award" Running with the Best (14:30), unknown; VHS Needs Case (Box 30, Video 588)
      - Tony Woods, unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 30, Video 590)
      - 1990 Football Season Tickets, VHS T-120 (Box 30, Video 592)
      - 1993-94 Pitt recruiting video, unknown; VHS T-30 Needs Case (Box 30, Video 595)
      - Pitt Recruiting Video (1986), VHS T-120 Needs Case (Box 30, Video 597)
      - Pittsburgh Football Halftimes -1991 - 1. "The Art of Snapping" / 2. "Paul Hackett Profile", unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 30, Video 599)
      - "Football Excellence" (with Mike Gottfried), unknown; VHS T-45 (Box 30, Video 600)
      - 1997 Pittsburgh (OFF) Cut-ups Red Zone I (1 of 2) Coach Harris, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 1 of 2 (Box 31, Video 629)
      - Red Zone I (2 of 2) 1997 Pittsburgh (OFF), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 2 of 2 Property of Coach Harris (Box 31, Video 624)
      - 1997 Pittsburgh (OFF) Cut-ups Red Zone II Coach Harris, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 31, Video 628)
      - Red Zone III 1997 Pittsburgh (OFF), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Property of Coach Harris (Box 31, Video 601)
      - 1997 Pittsburgh (OFF) Cut-ups Red Zone IV Coach Harris, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Property of Coach Harris (Box 31, Video 627)
      - Red Zone V 1997 Pittsburgh (OFF), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Property of Coach Harris (Box 31, Video 605)
      - 1997 Pittsburgh Panthers Self-Scout 3 & 1-2, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 31, Video 608)
      - 1997 Pittsburgh Panthers Self-Scout 4 & 1-2, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 31, Video 602)
      - 1997 Pittsburgh Panthers Self-Scout Slip Screen Left & Right, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 31, Video 612)
      - 1997 Pittsburgh Panthers Self-Scout 4 & 1-2, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 31, Video 610)
      - 1997 Pittsburgh Panther Self-Scout 56/57 Protection, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 31, Video 615)
      - 1997 Pittsburgh Panther Self-Scout 56/57 Protection, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 31, Video 618)
      - 1997 Pittsburgh Panthers Special Teams Punt 1 SW. Louisiana to Boston College, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 31, Video 603)
      - 1997 Pittsburgh Panthers Special Teams PAT/FG Miscues, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 31, Video 604)
      - 1997 Pittsburgh Panthers Special Teams 10 + Returns, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 31, Video 606)
      - 1997 Pittsburgh Panthers Special Teams Middle Wall Block, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 31, Video 607)
      - 1997 Pittsburgh Panthers Special Teams Punt - Pirate Skin Cat Double, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 31, Video 622)
      - 97 Pittsburgh (OFF) Cut-Up 4/5 Hole Runs (1 of 3) Coach Harris, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 1 of 3 Needs Case (Box 31, Video 617)
      - 97 Pittsburgh (OFF) Cut-Up 4/5 Hole Runs (2 of 3) Coach Harris, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 31, Video 619)
      - 97 Pittsburgh (OFF) Cut-Up 4/5 Hole Runs (3 of 3) Coach Harris, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 3 of 3 Needs Case (Box 31, Video 611)
      - 97 Pittsburgh (OFF) Cut-Ups 8/9 Hole Runs (1 of 2) Coach Harris, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 1 of 2 Needs Case (Box 31, Video 616)
      - '97 Pittsburgh (OFF) Cut-Ups 8/9 Hole Runs (2 of 2) Coach Harris, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 2 of 2 Needs Case (Box 31, Video 609)
      - Red Zone / As it Plays Out (1 of 4) 1997 Pittsburgh (OFF), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 1 of 4 Property of Coach Harris (Box 31, Video 626)
      - Red Zone / As it Plays Out (2 of 4) 1997 Pittsburgh (OFF), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 2 of 4 Property of Coach Harris (Box 31, Video 623)
      - Red Zone / As it Plays Out (3 of 4) 1997 Pittsburgh (OFF), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 3 of 4 Property of Coach Harris (Box 31, Video 625)
      - Red Zone / As it Plays Out (4 of 4) 1997 Pittsburgh (OFF), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 4 of 4 Property of Coach Harris (Box 31, Video 621)
      - DUCFLP 1997 Pittsburgh (OFF), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 31, Video 620)
      - 1997 Pittsburgh Panthers Base Offense, unknown; Betacam SP Needs Case (Box 31, Video 613)
      - University of Pittsburgh Big East Feed, October 11, 1993; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20s (Box 32, Video 631)
      - Pitt Big East Feed, October 11, 1993; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 (Box 32, Video 665)
      - Pitt Football, September 23, 1996; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 (Box 32, Video 634)
      - Pitt Football, October 21, 1996; 3/4 Inch U-matic 20BQ (Box 32, Video 660)
      - Pitt Football, November 11, 1996; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 (Box 32, Video 633)
      - Pitt Football, November 18, 1996; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 TRT 2:30 (Box 32, Video 666)
      - Pitt Football with Head Coach Johnny Majors, September 7, 1996; Betacam SP 28:30 TRT Show #2 (Box 32, Video 636)
      - Pitt Football vs WSU, August 2, 1995; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBR 20s (Box 32, Video 664)
      - Pitt Football vs Kent, September 9, 1996; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 (Box 32, Video 659)
      - Pitt Football vs Temple, October 7, 1996; 3/4 Inch U-matic 20BQ (Box 32, Video 663)
      - Pitt Football vs Virginia Tech, October 28, 1996; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 (Box 32, Video 658)
      - Rescue PKG & Porter PKG - For Larry Eldridge, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBR 20s Needs Case (Box 32, Video 667)
      - Dub - Pitt Football 1994, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 33, Video 671)
      - Pitt 4 Horsemen - Halftime Celeration[sic], October 15, 1994; Betacam SP 10 Minute (Box 33, Video 673)
      - Pitt - South Carolina Post game, October 13, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 Needs Case (Box 33, Video 674)
      - Pitt - South Carolina 1st Quarter, October 13, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 Needs Case (Box 33, Video 679)
      - Pitt - South Carolina 3rd Quarter, October 13, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 Needs Case (Box 33, Video 680)
      - Pitt - South Carolina 4th Quarter, October 13, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 Needs Case (Box 33, Video 681)
      - Pitt - Miami Post game, October 20, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 Needs Case (Box 33, Video 675)
      - Pitt - Miami 2nd Quarter, October 20, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 Tape 2 of 4 Needs Case (Box 33, Video 677)
      - Pitt - Miami 3rd Quarter, October 20, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 Tape 3 of 4 Needs Case (Box 33, Video 676)
      - Pitt - Miami 4th Quarter, October 20, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 Tape 4 of 4 Needs Case (Box 33, Video 678)
      - Pitt Homecoming, October 27, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 Tape 1 of 2 Needs Case (Box 33, Video 682)
      - Pitt Homecoming - Pitt vs. Navy, October 27, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 Tape 2 of 2 Needs Case (Box 33, Video 683)
      - PGM Record Pitt-NC State, October 12, 1985; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 2 of 4 (Box 33, Video 687)
      - PGM Record Pitt-NC State, October 12, 1985; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 4 of 4 (Box 33, Video 688)
      - Pitt - SMU 1, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 1 of ? Needs Case (Box 34, Video 706)
      - Pitt - SMU 2, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 2 of ? Needs Case (Box 34, Video 691)
      - Pitt vs. Boston College - Curvins Touchdown Run, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBR 20 (Box 34, Video 692)
      - WPXI-TV - Curvin Richards Special, VHS T-160 (Box 34, Video 694)
      - Curvin Richards Feature, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBR 20 Needs Case (Box 34, Video 699)
      - Mark Spindler (Profile), unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic BCS 20 (Box 34, Video 695)
      - Tony Woods Profile, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 (Box 34, Video 696)
      - Fralic Dub Okla., unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic Needs Case (Box 34, Video 698)
      - Charles Gladman Profile, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBU 5 Needs Case (Box 34, Video 700)
      - Pitt - N.D. '83 1, 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 1 of 4 Needs Case (Box 34, Video 704)
      - Pitt - N.D. '83 2, 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 2 of 4 Needs Case (Box 34, Video 702)
      - Pitt - N.D. '83 4, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 4 of 4 Needs Case (Box 34, Video 707)
      - ABC: Gator Bowl, March 15, 1990; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 35 Millimeter Tape Tape 1 of 2 Needs Case (Box 34, Video 703)
      - WV at Pitt, October 15, 1994; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 1 of 3 (Box 35, Video 708)
      - WV at Pitt, October 15, 1994; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 2 of 3 (Box 35, Video 709)
      - WV at Pitt, October 15, 1994; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 3 of 3 (Box 35, Video 710)
      - Pitt vs West Virginia - Field #2, October 15, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 (Box 35, Video 712)
      - Katz Sports - Pitt at South Carolina, October 17, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic 60 Minute Tape 4 of ? (Box 35, Video 711)
      - Pitt vs. Notre Dame, November 5, 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 30 (Box 35, Video 713)
      - Pitt / PSU Postgame, November 19, 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 35, Video 715)
      - Pitt vs. Arizona 1979 #2, December 24, 1979; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 2 of ? (Box 35, Video 716)
      - JP Sports - Great American Independent Football '89 (Navy @ Pitt), October 14, 1989; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 4 of 4 (Box 35, Video 717)
      - Pitt / Notre Dame, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCA 30 Tape 4 of 4 (Box 36, Video 719)
      - Pitt Project - Sugar Bowl / All That Jazz - Trip to N.O., unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 30 (Box 36, Video 720)
      - Pitt Project - "It's a Winner" - 1978 Highlights (film), unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBU-45 With time code window (Box 36, Video 721)
      - Pitt vs. WVU - Tape #2, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBR-20 Tape 2 of ? (Box 36, Video 726)
      - 11 WPXI-TV - Ironhead Heyward --- 1987 vs. BYU / vs. NC State, 3/4 Inch U-matic MBR-20s (Box 36, Video 727)
      - Pitt - Penn State, Part #2, November 24, 1978; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 2 of ? (Box 36, Video 728)
      - Pitt vs Texas, September 3, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 Tape 2 of ? (Box 37, Video 731)
      - Pitt vs Texas, September 3, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 Tape 3 of ? (Box 37, Video 735)
      - Pitt vs Texas, September 3, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 Tape 4 of ? (Box 37, Video 730)
      - Pitt vs. Texas - Tape #3, September 3, 1994; Betacam SP 60 Minute Tape 3 of ? (Box 37, Video 738)
      - Pitt vs Temple - Field #4 / Lockerroom, October 29, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 Tape 4 of ? (Box 37, Video 736)
      - Pitt vs Temple - Field #4 (Locker Room), October 29, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 Needs Case (Box 41, Video 868)
      - Highlights Pitt vs Temple, November 2, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 Master (Box 37, Video 737)
      - Pitt / Syracuse 2nd Quarter, November 3, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 Needs Case (Box 37, Video 740)
      - Pitt - Syracuse 4th Quarter, November 3, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 Needs Case (Box 37, Video 739)
      - Pitt / Syracuse Post game, November 3, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 Needs Case (Box 37, Video 741)
      - The Winning Tradition - 1982 Pre-game, 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 37, Video 742)
      - Pitt vs. Army - Reel #1, October 13, 1982; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 1 of ? Show Master (Box 37, Video 743)
      - The Johnny Majors Show - Show #3, September 17, 1994; VHS T-30 Needs Case (Box 40, Video 853)
      - Johnny Majors Show #3, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 30 (Box 38, Video 752)
      - Johnny Majors Show #3 - Raw Footage, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20s (Box 38, Video 744)
      - The Johnny Majors Show #3 - Raw Footage, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20s (Box 38, Video 745)
      - The Jonny Majors Show - Show #8 - (Split Audio), October 23, 1993; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 38, Video 762)
      - Panther Football with Head Coach Johnny Majors - Show #12, November 11, 1995; Betacam SP TRT 28:30 Master (Box 38, Video 749)
      - The Johnny Majors Show - Show #13 (Audio is Split on BOTH Sides), November 27, 1993; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCA 30 TRT 28:20 Master (Box 38, Video 750)
      - The Johnny Majors Show - Show #13 (Split Audio), November 27, 1993; Betacam SP 30 Minute TRT 28:30 (Box 38, Video 759)
      - Johnny Majors Halftime Feature - Big East Network: Teri Schindler, Chris Farrow, unknown; VHS Needs Case (Box 38, Video 747)
      - Integra Bank Quarterly Meeting Speaker: Johnny Majors, unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 38, Video 746)
      - Johnny Majors Audio, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic BCA-60 (Box 38, Video 751)
      - Johnny Majors (Blood Drive), unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 Tape 1 of ? (Box 38, Video 758)
      - "Giving Blood" Pitt - John Majors (Blood Drive), unknown; Betacam SP 5 Minute Needs Case (Box 40, Video 863)
      - Majors-Kids(?), unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 38, Video 760)
      - Majors Interview, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 38, Video 761)
      - Majors Mike #2, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 2 of ? Needs Case (Box 38, Video 768)
      - Majors Miked #3, October 2, 1993; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 3 of ? Needs Case (Box 38, Video 775)
      - Majors Miked #4, October 2, 1993; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 4 of ? Needs Case (Box 38, Video 764)
      - Majors Miked #4, October 2, 1993; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 4 of ? Needs Case (Box 38, Video 776)
      - Majors Miked #5, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 5 of ? Needs Case (Box 38, Video 763)
      - Video Clips From Panther Football with Head Coach Johnny Majors, unknown; VHS T-15 Needs Case (Box 39, Video 798)
      - John Majors (Press Conf.) (First Press Conf.), unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 40, Video 842)
      - Ron Dickebum at Clemson (def. Coord.) / Johnny Majors at Tennessee (head coach) - (Fall 1992 ESPN), Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 38, Video 753)
      - Pitt Football / John Majors Locker Raw Footage, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 41, Video 899)
      - Pitt vs. West Virginia #2, September 29, ????; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 Pratt Tape 2 of ? Needs Case (Box 39, Video 780)
      - Pitt vs WVU #3, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBR 20s Tape 3 of ? Needs Case (Box 39, Video 779)
      - Pitt - Texas Hilites (Big East Feed), unknown; Betacam SP 5 Minute (Box 39, Video 783)
      - Pitt vs. East Carolina Highlights, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic Needs Case (Box 39, Video 784)
      - "Pitt vs WVU" (1991 Season at WVU), VHS T-120 (Box 39, Video 795)
      - 1996 Colts PBP Sweepstakes Recap, January 12, 1997; VHS TRT 4:23 (Box 39, Video 796)
      - Pittsburgh vs. S.W. Louisiana - 1997, Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 39, Video 800)
      - Rueben Brown Pitt Football #78, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 41, Video 882)
      - Ruben Brown Pitt Football #78, unknown; Betacam SP (Box 41, Video 898)
      - Reuben Brown - LT #78, ISO Camera vs. Ohio ST, 1994, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 39, Video 802)
      - Ruben Brown - LT #78 (Isolation Camera vs. Ohio State) 1994, Betacam SP (damaged top) (Box 41, Video 893)
      - Ruben Brown vs. Ohio State, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 41, Video 886)
      - Reuben Brown vs. Ohio State, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 41, Video 888)
      - "Jack Ham and Joe Paterno" (LionVison), April 20, 1989; VHS T-15 (Box 39, Video 803)
      - "Alex Van Pelt and Pitt Defense", April 9, ????; Betacam SP (Box 39, Video 808)
      - "The 1992 Doak Walker Award" (Best College Running Back), VHS T-15 (Box 39, Video 811)
      - Ohio State Self Off 1996 - Redzones Tape 1, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 39, Video 821)
      - Pitt vs Boston College #3, September 8, 1990; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 39, Video 825)
      - BC at Pitt - ISOS, September 24, 1994; Betacam SP 20 Minute Needs Case (Box 39, Video 828)
      - 1984 Football Highlights, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBU 5 (Box 40, Video 830)
      - Pitt Football Camp #1, August 14, 1990; Betacam SP 20 Minute Tape 1 of ? Tuesday AM Needs Case (Box 40, Video 840)
      - Pitt Football Camp #2 (Tuesday morning), August 14, 1990; Betacam SP 20 Minute Tape 2 of ? Tuesday AM (Box 40, Video 858)
      - Pitt Football Camp #3, August 14, 1990; Betacam SP 20 Minute Tape 3 of ? Tuesday PM Needs Case (Box 40, Video 865)
      - Pitt Football Camp #4, August 14, 1990; Betacam SP 20 Minute Tape 4 of ? Tuesday PM Needs Case (Box 40, Video 864)
      - Pitt Football Camp #9, August 15, 1990; Betacam SP 20 Minute Wednesday PM (Box 40, Video 831)
      - Pitt Camp #10, August 16, 1990; Betacam SP 20 Minute Thursday AM w/ Hackett (Box 40, Video 832)
      - Pitt Camp Football #12, August 16, 1990; Betacam SP 20 Minute Tape 12 of ? Thursday AM (Box 40, Video 843)
      - Pitt Football Camp #14, August 16, 1990; Betacam SP 20 Minute Tape 14 of ? Thursday PM w/ Hackett (Box 40, Video 866)
      - Pitt Football Camp #16, August 17, 1990; Betacam SP 20 Minute Tape 16 of ? Friday AM/PM (Box 40, Video 838)
      - "Pitt vs PSU" (Tape #1), unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute Tape 1 of ? (Box 40, Video 833)
      - "Pitt vs. PSU" (Tape #2), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 2 of ? (Box 40, Video 834)
      - "Pitt vs Penn State" (Tape #2), unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute Tape 2 of ? (Box 40, Video 844)
      - "Pitt vs Penn State" (Tape #3), unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute Tape 3 of ? (Box 40, Video 841)
      - "Pitt vs. Penn State" (Tape #4), unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute Tape 4 of ? (Box 40, Video 836)
      - "Pitt vs. Syracuse" - Tape #1, October 19, 1991; Betacam SP 20 Minute Tape 1 of ? (Box 40, Video 848)
      - "Pitt vs. Syracuse" (Tape #2), October 19, 1991; Betacam SP 20 Minute Tape 2 of ? (Box 40, Video 837)
      - "Pitt vs. Syracuse" - Tape #3, October 19, 1991; Betacam SP 20 Minute Tape 3 of ? (Box 40, Video 835)
      - 1991 Pitt Football vs Syracuse, unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 40, Video 850)
      - "1991 Pitt Homecoming vs Syracuse", unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 40, Video 845)
      - 11 News - West Signs Pitt, unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 41, Video 867)
      - Pitt vs Rutgers - 1st Quarter 10/13/1990, October 13, 1990; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 41, Video 869)
      - Pitt vs. Syracuse - 4th Quarter, September 22, 1990; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 41, Video 870)
      - Pitt player stills, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 Needs Case (Box 41, Video 873)
      - "Keith Hamilton" (Profile), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 41, Video 871)
      - Marty Schottenheimer, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 41, Video 875)
      - Sean Gilbert Profile - 1991, Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 41, Video 877)
      - "Sean Gilbert" (Profile), unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 41, Video 879)
      - "Sean Gilbert" (Profile), unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 41, Video 900)
      - Pitt Parade - Pitt Football, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic EK 20 (Box 41, Video 880)
      - Pitt @ Syr ISOS, October 8, 1994; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 41, Video 881)
      - Football Season 1990, unknown; Betacam SP 5 Minute Needs Case (Box 41, Video 883)
      - Temple at Pitt ISOs, October 29, 1994; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 41, Video 885)
      - Pitt Off. vs. Oklahoma - End Zone, September 15, 1990; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 41, Video 894)
      - Paul Martha - Pitt, unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 41, Video 895)
      - Foge Fazio - Player and Coach, unknown; Betacam SP (Box 41, Video 897)
      - Ohio State - 1996 Selft Off 3rd. Downs - Tape1, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 1 of ? (Box 42, Video 904)
      - Ohio State - 1996 Selft Off 3rd. Downs - Tape2, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 2 of ? (Box 42, Video 919)
      - Ohio State Self Off 1996 - Redzones Tape 2, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 2 of ? (Box 42, Video 925)
      - 1A Football Play-off Research Group, unknown; VHS T-60 (Box 42, Video 906)
      - SW Louisiana (Special Teams) vs. Va. Tech 1996, VHS (Box 42, Video 909)
      - ABC Program CFA - Part 3 of 4, November 28, 1980; 3/4 Inch U-matic BCA 60 Tape 3 of 4 (Box 42, Video 916)
      - 1983 Football Season, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 Needs Case (Box 42, Video 918)
      - Couch Potato Commercial - Football Scenes, unknown; Betacam SP (Box 42, Video 920)
      - Pitt - Notre Dame #1, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 1 of ? Needs Case (Box 42, Video 922)
      - Pitt - Notre Dame #2, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 2 of ? Needs Case (Box 42, Video 923)
      - Pitt - Notre Dame #3, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 3 of ? Needs Case (Box 42, Video 929)
      - Pitt - Notre Dame #4, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 4 of ? Needs Case (Box 42, Video 934)
      - Pitt Fla St. - 1 Qtr, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Needs Case (Box 42, Video 927)
      - Pitt Fla. St - 2QT, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Needs Case (Box 42, Video 932)
      - Pitt Fla. St. - 3 Qtr., unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic Needs Case (Box 42, Video 924)
      - Pitt Fla. St - 4Qtr, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Needs Case (Box 42, Video 937)
      - Pitt - OSU ('83), unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 1 of ? Needs Case (Box 42, Video 931)
      - Pitt - OSU - 2, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 2 of ? Needs Case (Box 42, Video 933)
      - Pitt - OSU ('83) 3, 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 3 of ? Needs Case (Box 42, Video 928)
      - Pitt - OSU - 4, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 4 of ? Needs Case (Box 42, Video 930)
      - "Dynasty" Teaser Promo Reel #2 - :30 Promos, Shows #20-#79, September 6, 1985; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 43, Video 950)
      - KBL Sportsbeat - Paul Hackett, unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 43, Video 955)
      - Hula Bowl 1983, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Needs Case (Box 44, Video 975)